Your face is a little erotic.
少し顔がエロいね
I caught it, so let me carry it for a while.
引っ掛けたからちょっと運んでもらおう、
everyone.
みんな
Take it back.
取り返して
And go outside.
そして外に行ってください
Please lick it while thanking me properly.
ちゃんと感謝しながら舐めてね
Because there are times when there is a change.
交代の際には際もあるから
Lick it to the jingle.
ジングルに舐めて
Hand-finish the untamed artificial material.
舐めてない人工を手で仕上げて
Don't forget that.
それを忘れてはダメだよ
What should I do with my hands?
手はどうするんだっけ?
Well done.
よくできました
Shall we go together?
一緒に行こうよっか
Try it.
やってみて
You can do it.
できるじゃん
Everyone is getting better.
み んな元気になってきたね
What's next?
次どうするの?
What will you do when you grow up?
大きくなったらどうするんですか?
put in.
入れる
Please go again.
もう一回行けて
I haven't put anything in there.
何も入れてないよ
Did you say you put it in?
入れたって言ったの?
What should I do first?
最初どうしようか?
No matter what system you put in.
どの体制入れても
You can do what your mother likes.
お母さんの人が好きなのをすればいい
Are you saying something?
何か言ってる?
oh dear.
まあ
Damn it, it's here.
くよ、来たよ
It's here.
来 たよ
Even this.
これでもさ
That's good.
いいよね
Good, not good.
いいよくない
Isn't it good?
いいよくないか
It's not good, but it's good.
いいよくないけど、いいよね
Good Not good.
いい よくない
No?
ダメ?
Let's add a book.
本を付けよう
I'll do it in my first year.
一回生でやる
From ahead.
先から
I might just go with Mikosei and a half.
みこせい半でいっちゃうかもしれないでしょ
Just a little bit.
少しだけ
Just a little bit, right?
ちょっとでしょ
Did you feel better?
気持ちよくなっちゃった?
Because it's actually multiple.
ちゃんと複数だからね
It feels good for just one minute.
1分だけ気持ちよくなのだね
I want to say it too.
俺も言いたい
Saya-tan, it's okay.
さやたん、ちょっといいよ
I'm spoiled too.
俺も甘えちゃって
good?
いい?
It felt good.
気持ちよくなっちゃった
Ah, I went here.
あ、ここに行ってきた
Make sure to move your hips, hands, and mouth.
ちゃんと腰と手と口と全部動かすな
Saya-tan, you haven't even gone as far as that cock.
さやたん、そっちのチンポンまで行ってないでしょ
Let's make that dick more energetic.
そっちのチンポンを元気にしてあげてもっと
How are you?
元気かな?
Are you feeling better too?
そっちも元気になった?
Is it okay to say that if I'm fine?
元気だったらそれ言ってもいいの?
that
それ
Can I tell you?
言 ってもいいの?
The next one.
次の1つ
Must be painful?
きっと苦しい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Can I go okay?
ちゃんと行ってもいい?
Where should I ride it?
どこに乗せばいい?
TRUE?
本当?
nice.
いいね
Wouldn't it be nice if you could show it to me?
見 せてもらえたらいいんじゃない?
Could you please show me?
見せてもらえたらいい?
This is your first time seeing it, right?
初めて見るでしょ?
I can't see it.
見えない
Can you see it this way?
こうやってやったら見える?
It's coming out really well.
すごく出てるよ
Because this is gear.
これがギアルだからね
Please continue riding this way.
このまま乗っかってください
Leave it for next time.
もう 次にしといて
Because I'm really fine.
めちゃめちゃ元気だから
Do you sleep too much?
寝るすぎる?
I sleep too much.
寝る寝るすぎるんだって
Sena-chan.
せなちゃん
I sleep too much.
寝る寝るすぎる
really like.
大好き
Be careful.
注意だね
It's definitely warm.
確かに温かいよ
It's warm.
温かいよ
Shall I introduce you?
紹介しよっか
Do you mean don't move on?
進むなってこと?
Push me.
押し付けて
I'm forcing something.
なんか押し付けてる
fall
落
We're just getting there.
ち 着きだしとこな
Push it yourself.
自分で押し付けて
自 分 で 押し付けて
Sena-chan, when you're doing this, there's an amazing smell of semen.
せ なちゃん、これやってると すごい精子の匂いがする
That's amazing, the one you just brought out.
すごいよ、さっき出されたやつ
what up?
どうした?
There are some dry people out there.
乾いた人がいるな
take care.
気を付けて
Take care
気を
Attach it.
付 けて
take care.
気を付けて
It's actually swollen.
腫 れてるよ、もともと
Sena-chan.
せなちゃん
See for yourself.
見てごらん、自分で
Don't you love it?
大好きじゃない?
That's amazing, I love it.
すごいよ、好きだよね
Is this really what you want?
これ、本骨作る?
I feel like it's still coming out.
まだ出てきてる気がする
show me.
見せて
It's starting to get kind of bubbly.
なんか泡々になってきた
I'll post it here too.
出すよ、ここにも
good?
いい?
I fired three shots, I'm sure it was just one.
3発も出しちゃったね、きっと1発で
Too much.
出 しすぎ
I put out too much.
出しすぎちゃった
It's going to be amazing.
すごいことになってる
It's so white that I can't tell if it's coming out or not.
出てるのか、出てないのか、分からないくらいは真っ白
it hurts?
痛い?
Okay, that angle is fine.
いいよ、その角度でいい
look?
見る?
Take a look.
ちょっと見て
Did you see it?
見えた?
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's your first time.
初めてだよね
It's not over yet.
まだ終わりじゃないんだよね
Isn't it over yet?
まだ終わりじゃないの?
I'm still fine.
まだ元気なんで
It's so pushy that everyone can't stand it in front of them.
押しだから、目の前にしてみんな我慢できないらしい
I guess I'll just keep doing this for a while.
ちょっと、このままやっちゃおうかな
What should I do?
どうしたら?
One more time.
もう1回
One more round.
もう1回戦
About 3 rounds.
3ラウンドくらい
What about round 3?
3ラウンドは?
Oh no, no no.
やばい、やばい
Instead of taking a short break, I drink tea once.
ちょっとだけ、休憩じゃなくて、1回お茶飲む
drink tea.
お茶飲む
OK, that's it.
OK、じゃあそれでね